<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<options>

  <!-- 
  Debug Options
  -->
  
  <option
        ID="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_DebugVerbosity"
        DisplayText="{{y|Ductape Mod}}: Verbosity of debug entries output to Player.log"
        Category="Debug"
        Type="Slider" 
        Default="0"
        Min="0"
        Max="4"
        Increment="1" >
		<helptext>
      {{g|0}}: Only infrequnet entries will be sent to Player.log, and only for reporting on normal function.
      {{W|1}}: Debug entries will be sent to Player.log when certain functions are perfomed within this mod.
      {{o|2}}: More frequent Player.log entries for a wider array of functions, often tracing broad program flow.
      {{r|3}}: Even more Player.log entries including current internal values as they're passed around.
      {{R|4}}: {{R|Not Recommended}} | Maximum number of entries to Player.log including tracing common or frequent loops.

      The value default is {{g|0}}.
    </helptext>
	</option>
	
  <option
        ID="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_DebugIncludeInMessage"
		    Requires="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_DebugVerbosity!=0"
        DisplayText="{{y|Ductape Mod}}: Also show debug entries in the Message Queue"
        Category="Debug"
        Type="Checkbox"
        Default="No" >
    <helptext>
      When enabled, debug entries will be sent to the Message Queue any time (with few exceptions) they would be sent to Player.log.
      At higher levels of verbosity, this can be {{r|very}} "loud" and spammy.

      The default is {{w|Disabled}}.
    </helptext>
  </option>
	
  <option
        ID="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_DebugDuctapeModDescriptions"
        DisplayText="{{y|Ductape Mod}}: Show Ductape Mod internal debug information in relevant ShortDescriptions displayed in the [{{W|l}}]ook UI."
        Category="Debug"
        Type="Checkbox"
        Default="No" >
    <helptext>
      When enabled, internal debug information relating to the &quot;held together by utilitape&quot; modification will be displayed when [{{W|l}}]ooking at anything with the relevant parts.

      {{M|Ductape}}:
      {{W|Stats}}: Shows statistical information about the modification's performance.

      The default is {{w|Disabled}}.
    </helptext>
  </option>
  
  <!-- 
  Mod Options
  -->
  <option
        ID="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_AnyNumberOfMods"
        DisplayText="Enable &quot;held together by utilitape&quot; to be applied before an item has the maximum mods applied."
        Category="Mod: UD Ductape Mod"
        Type="Checkbox"
        Default="No" >
    <helptext>
      When enabled, &quot;held together by utilitape&quot; can be applied to otherwise eligable items irrespective of how many mods they already have applied.

      The default behaviour is that the mod can only be applied to items that already have the maximum number of mods.

      This is largely because the destructive nature of the mod combined with the fact that its only benefit comes when already maxed out on mods means it's typically a poor decision to apply it before wanting to apply a fourth mod.

      The default is {{w|Disabled}}.
    </helptext>
  </option>
  
  <option
        ID="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_ScalingDamageChance"
		    Requires="Option_UD_Ductape_Mod_AnyNumberOfMods"
        DisplayText="Enable scaling the chance &quot;held together by utilittape&quot; will damage an item according to how many mods are applied."
        Category="Mod: UD Ductape Mod"
        Type="Checkbox"
        Default="No" >
    <helptext>
      When enabled, &quot;held together by utilitape&quot; will take into account how many mods are currently applied to an item when determining how likely the item will be damaged while being used.
      
      Excluding utilitape, the following schedule lays out the adjustment to damage chance:
      {{G|0}}: won't be damaged.
      {{g|1}}: 1/4 as likely
      {{W|2}}: 1/3 as likely
      {{r|3}}: 1/2 as likely
      {{R|4}}: 1/1 as likely (capped)

      The default is {{w|Disabled}}.
    </helptext>
  </option>

  <!-- End of Mod Options -->
  
</options>